Explore Gold IRAs
    
    * [
        
        Gold IRA: the Basics](https://goldalliance.com/learning-center/gold/gold-ira-the-basics/)

    Resources
    
    * [Featured News

        New “Anti-Surveillance” Bill Joins Battle to Block CBDCs 
        
        View Article](https://goldalliance.com/blog/market-insights/new-anti-surveillance-bill-joins-battle-to-block-cbdcs/)

    About
    
    * [
        
        Learn More About Us](https://goldalliance.com/about/)

Privacy Policy
==============

**_Last updated:_** June 22, 2023 

Thank you for visiting [https://goldalliance.com](https://goldalliance.com/) (the “Site”), a property of Gold Alliance Capital Inc. (“Gold Alliance”), in addition to the following web properties: goldalliedtrust.com, theunitedgoldtrust.com, americangoldcapital.com, theusgoldtrust.com, citizensgoldtrust.com, (the “Gold Alliance Sites”).  

You must be at least 18 years old to use the Site and the Gold Alliance Sites.  

We take your privacy very seriously. Please read this Privacy Policy carefully as it contains important information on how and why we collect, store, use, and share your personal information when you use this Site and any of the Gold Alliance Sites. It also explains your rights in relation to your personal information and how to contact us. 

By accessing, using, or submitting information to the Site or any of the Gold Alliance Sites, you agree to this Privacy Policy and our Terms & Conditions. 

**Personal Information We Collect About You and How We Use It** 

We have collected personal information about consumers within the preceding twelve (12) months in the following categories:  

| Categories of Personal Information | We Collect  <br>(Yes/No) | Categories of Sources from Which PI is Collected | Business Purpose | Length of Retention |
| --- | --- | --- | --- | --- |
| Identifiers (e.g., a real name, alias, postal address, unique personal identifier, online identifier, Internet Protocol address, email address, account name, social security number, driver’s license number, passport number, or other similar identifiers), or information that identifies, relates to, describes, or is capable of being associated with, a particular individual | Yes | Consumer Directly  <br>  <br>Advertising Networks  <br>  <br>ISPs  <br>  <br>Data analytics providers | ​​Auditing related to counting ad impressions to unique visitors, verifying positioning and quality of ad impressions, and auditing compliance with this specification and other standards  <br>  <br>Helping to ensure security and integrity;  <br>  <br>Debugging to identify and repair errors that impair existing intended functionality.  <br>  <br>Short-term, transient use, provided that the personal information is not disclosed to another third party and is not used to build a profile about a consumer or otherwise alter an individual consumer’s experience outside the current interaction, including, but not limited to, the contextual customization of ads shown as part of the same interaction.  <br>  <br>Performing services on behalf of the business or service provider, including maintaining or servicing accounts, providing customer service, processing or fulfilling orders and transactions, verifying customer information, processing payments, providing financing, providing advertising or marketing services, providing analytic services, or providing similar services on behalf of the business or service provider.  <br>  <br>Undertaking internal research for technological development and demonstration.  <br>  <br>Undertaking activities to verify or maintain the quality or safety of a service or device that is owned, manufactured, manufactured for, or controlled by the business, and to improve, upgrade, or enhance the service or device that is owned, manufactured, manufactured for, or controlled by the business. | Retention is currently indefinite for this information unless specifically requested to remove. |
| Characteristics of protected calssifications under California or federal law | No  | Not applicable |     |     |
| Commercial information | Yes | Consumer Directly  <br>  <br>Advertising networks  <br>  <br>Data analytics providers | Auditing related to counting ad impressions to unique visitors, verifying positioning and quality of ad impressions, and auditing compliance with this specification and other standards  <br>  <br>Helping to ensure security and integrity  <br>  <br>Debugging to identify and repair errors that impair existing intended functionality.  <br>  <br>Short-term, transient use, provided that the personal information is not disclosed to another third party and is not used to build a profile about a consumer or otherwise alter an individual consumer’s experience outside the current interaction, including, but not limited to, the contextual customization of ads shown as part of the same interaction.  <br>  <br>Performing services on behalf of the business or service provider, including maintaining or servicing accounts, providing customer service, processing or fulfilling orders and transactions, verifying customer information, processing payments, providing financing, providing advertising or marketing services, providing analytic services, or providing similar services on behalf of the business or service provider.  <br>  <br>Undertaking internal research for technological development and demonstration.  <br>  <br>​ Undertaking activities to verify or maintain the quality or safety of a service or device that is owned, manufactured, manufactured for, or controlled by the business, and to improve, upgrade, or enhance the service or device that is owned, manufactured, manufactured for, or controlled by the business. | Retention is currently indefinite for this information unless specifically requested to remove. |
| Biometric information | No  | Not applicable |     |     |
| Internet or other electronic network activity information (e.g., browsing history, search history, and information regarding a consumer’s interaction with a website, application, or advertisement) | Yes | Consumer directly  <br>  <br>Advertising networks  <br>  <br>ISPs  <br>  <br>Data analytics providers | ​​Auditing related to counting ad impressions to unique visitors, verifying positioning and quality of ad impressions, and auditing compliance with this specification and other standards  <br>  <br>Helping to ensure security and integrity;  <br>  <br>​​Debugging to identify and repair errors that impair existing intended functionality.  <br>  <br>​​Short-term, transient use, provided that the personal information is not disclosed to another third party and is not used to build a profile about a consumer or otherwise alter an individual consumer’s experience outside the current interaction, including, but not limited to, the contextual customization of ads shown as part of the same interaction.  <br>  <br>​​Performing services on behalf of the business or service provider, including maintaining or servicing accounts, providing customer service, processing or fulfilling orders and transactions, verifying customer information, processing payments, providing financing, providing advertising or marketing services, providing analytic services, or providing similar services on behalf of the business or service provider.  <br>  <br>​​Undertaking internal research for technological development and demonstration.  <br>  <br>​​Undertaking activities to verify or maintain the quality or safety of a service or device that is owned, manufactured, manufactured for, or controlled by the business, and to improve, upgrade, or enhance the service or device that is owned, manufactured, manufactured for, or controlled by the business. | Retention is currently indefinite for this information unless specifically requested to remove. |
| Geolocation data | Yes | Consumer directly  <br>  <br>Advertising networks  <br>  <br>ISPs  <br>  <br>Data analytics providers | Auditing related to counting ad impressions to unique visitors, verifying positioning and quality of ad impressions, and auditing compliance with this specification and other standards  <br>  <br>​​Helping to ensure security and integrity;  <br>  <br>​​Debugging to identify and repair errors that impair existing intended functionality.  <br>  <br>​​Short-term, transient use, provided that the personal information is not disclosed to another third party and is not used to build a profile about a consumer or otherwise alter an individual consumer’s experience outside the current interaction, including, but not limited to, the contextual customization of ads shown as part of the same interaction.  <br>  <br>​​Performing services on behalf of the business or service provider, including maintaining or servicing accounts, providing customer service, processing or fulfilling orders and transactions, verifying customer information, processing payments, providing financing, providing advertising or marketing services, providing analytic services, or providing similar services on behalf of the business or service provider.  <br>  <br>​​Undertaking internal research for technological development and demonstration.  <br>  <br>​​Undertaking activities to verify or maintain the quality or safety of a service or device that is owned, manufactured, manufactured for, or controlled by the business, and to improve, upgrade, or enhance the service or device that is owned, manufactured, manufactured for, or controlled by the business. | Retention is currently indefinite for this information unless specifically requested to remove. |
| Audio, electronic, visual, thermal, olfactory, or similar information | No  | Not applicable |     |     |
| Professional or employment-related information | No  | Not applicable |     |     |
| Education information | No  | Not applicable |     |     |
| Inferences drawn from any of the information identified above to create a profile about a consumer reflecting their preferences, characteristics, psychological trends, predispositions, behavior, attitudes, intelligence, abilities, and aptitudes | Yes | Consumer directly  <br>  <br>Advertising networks  <br>  <br>ISPs  <br>  <br>Data analytics providers | Auditing related to counting ad impressions to unique visitors, verifying positioning and quality of ad impressions, and auditing compliance with this specification and other standards  <br>  <br>​​Helping to ensure security and integrity;  <br>  <br>​​Debugging to identify and repair errors that impair existing intended functionality.  <br>  <br>​​Short-term, transient use, provided that the personal information is not disclosed to another third party and is not used to build a profile about a consumer or otherwise alter an individual consumer’s experience outside the current interaction, including, but not limited to, the contextual customization of ads shown as part of the same interaction.  <br>  <br>​​Performing services on behalf of the business or service provider, including maintaining or servicing accounts, providing customer service, processing or fulfilling orders and transactions, verifying customer information, processing payments, providing financing, providing advertising or marketing services, providing analytic services, or providing similar services on behalf of the business or service provider.  <br>  <br>​​Undertaking internal research for technological development and demonstration.  <br>  <br>​​Undertaking activities to verify or maintain the quality or safety of a service or device that is owned, manufactured, manufactured for, or controlled by the business, and to improve, upgrade, or enhance the service or device that is owned, manufactured, manufactured for, or controlled by the business. | Retention is currently indefinite for this information unless specifically requested to remove. |
| Sensitive personal information | No  | Not applicable |     |     |

As noted in the chart above, we collect the above personal information directly from you via the Site, and from your interactions with the Site, including any personal information which you provide directly or indirectly.  

Indirectly 

Cookies and Tracking Pixels on the Site: We use and store cookies and tracking pixels on the Site, as described further herein. A cookie is a small data text file containing an identifier (a string of letters and numbers) that is sent by a web server to a web browser and which is stored on your computer’s web browser. The identifier is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. Cookies can later be retrieved to identify you to us. Personal information that we store about you may be linked to the information stored in and obtained from cookies. Cookies make your use of the Site easier, make the Site run more smoothly, and help us to maintain a secure Site. Tracking pixels (also known as web beacons, 1×1 pixels, or clear GIFs) are code requiring a call back to a server to render, and which deliver information to us about your IP address and information from your browser. Cookies and tracking pixels are used to track your interaction with the Site, including clicks. Cookies and tracking pixels may collect information about you, such as your IP address, your browser type and version, operating system, software and platform, your Internet service provider, geographic location, the area code and zip code associated with your server, time zone setting, the date and time of your visit, the time spent on the Site, referring and exit domain names and websites, screen resolutions, color capabilities, browser plug-ins, language settings, cookie preferences, search engine keywords, and clickstream data.  

In addition to the above, we utilize third party service provider, ActiveCampaign, to provide a tracking feature for the Site. ActiveCampaign uses first-party cookies to track visits to the Site and associates those visits with our records. ActiveCampaign collects the IP address of any our contacts visiting the Site, and also tracks interactions with the Site, such as clicks on a link and webform submission. By visiting the Site and interacting with the Site, you consent to such collection, tracking, and storage. 

Cookies and Tracking Pixels in Our Emails: Apart from our use of the above technologies on our Site, we automatically collect information when an individual opens an email marketing the Site or the Gold Alliance Sites, through the use of cookies and tracking pixels. We also automatically collect information on whether the individual clicked on any links within such emails. 

You can instruct your web browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent, by visiting the preferences or settings page of your web browser. In the event that your browser requests that we do not track you or store a cookie, unless otherwise required by law to honor the requests, we do not guarantee that our Site will honor such requests. Please note that we do not guarantee that the Site will work properly in the event that you elect to opt out of our tracking or use of cookies.  

Directly

To the extent that you contact us through the Site, we collect the personal information you submit, including your name and email address. 

To the extent that you utilize the chat box feature on the Site, you understand that we utilize third party service providers, including Drift, that record and store a transcript of any chat history for the purposes of documentation and quality assurance, and you consent to such recording and storage. 

To the extent that you like our social media profile by clicking on the button featured on the Site, we may link such activities and any personal information with the personal information we have collected.  

To the extent that you request to receive our guides, resources, and materials, and/or subscribe to receive our email newsletter, we collect the personal information you submit, including your first name, last name, email address, and phone number. We use this information to send you information that may be of interest to you, including by email and phone, as noted below.  

Email: In connection with your subscription to our newsletter, we also collect information on whether you viewed the email newsletter and clicked on any links within such email newsletters. If you do not want us to communicate with you about other offers regarding our products, programs, materials, or services by email, postal mail, or telephone, you may unsubscribe through the unsubscribe link featured in the email. If you request to unsubscribe from receiving emails from us, we will add your email address to our suppression file, to comply with CAN-SPAM.  

Phone: In connection with your registration on the Site, you agree that such act constitutes an inquiry and/or application for purposes of the Amended Telemarketing Sales Rule (16 CFR § 310 et seq.), as amended from time to time and applicable state do-not-call regulations. As such, notwithstanding that your telephone number may be listed on the Federal Trade Commission’s Do-Not-Call List, and/or on applicable state do-not-call lists, we retain the right to contact you via telemarketing in accordance with the such and applicable federal and state do-not-call regulations. 

In addition, you agree that by submitting your personal information through the Site, you agree to receive mobile marketing including, but not limited to, text-message based marketing, from us (where such marketing is permitted by applicable law). As such, notwithstanding that your mobile telephone number may be listed on state and/or federal Do-Not-Call registries, we retain the right to contact you via text-message based marketing in accordance with applicable state and federal law.  

This site is compliant with the Telephone Consumer Protection Act as implemented by the Federal Communications Commission. By entering the information requested on the fields on the Site and clicking “YES!- GET MY FREE GUIDE” (or similar button), you agree by electronic signature to our Terms & Conditions (including our arbitration provision and E-SIGN consent) and this Privacy Policy and give explicit consent (not required as a condition to purchase a good/service) for us to contact you (including through the use of automated means, auto-dialers, pre-recorded messages, and text messages) via telephone, mobile device (including SMS and MMS), and/or email, even if your phone is a mobile number or is listed on a corporate, state or national Do Not Call registry. Message and data rates may apply. If you do not wish to consent to the above but wish to obtain information about our services or the advertised guide, please call us at 888-734-7453. 

From Third Parties 

As noted above in the chart, in addition to collecting personal information through the Site, we also collect personal information through third party advertising networks, Internet service providers (“ISPs”), and data analytics providers. We also use third party service provider ActiveCampaign to track visits to the Site and associate those visits with our own records. ActiveCampaign collects the IP address of any contacts visiting the Site, and also tracks interactions with the Site, such as clicks on a link and form submission. More information on ActiveCampaign can be viewed here: [https://help.activecampaign.com/hc/en-us/articles/221542267-An-overview-of-Site-Tracking#an-overview-of-site-tracking-0-0](https://help.activecampaign.com/hc/en-us/articles/221542267-An-overview-of-Site-Tracking#an-overview-of-site-tracking-0-0) and for information regarding how such data may be used, please see: [https://www.activecampaign.com/legal/terms-of-service](https://www.activecampaign.com/legal/terms-of-service)  

To the extent that you utilize the chat box feature on the Site, third party service providers, including Drift, may record and store a transcript of any chat history for the purposes of documentation and quality assurance. More information on Drift can be viewed here: [https://gethelp.drift.com/s/article/Wiretapping-FAQ](https://gethelp.drift.com/s/article/Wiretapping-FAQ)  

**With Whom Do We Share Your Information**  

We may share the above information with third party service provider ActiveCampaign to utilize its tracking services, and associate Site visits with our own records 

We may also share the above information with our marketing partners, such as third party advertising networks and email publishers, for the purpose of tracking clicks/conversions to our Site. Also, if you request to unsubscribe from receiving email newsletters from us, we may share your email address with such marketing partners to effectuate your request to unsubscribe and to comply with CAN-SPAM. 

Also, on occasion, we may be required by law enforcement or judicial authorities to provide information to the appropriate governmental authorities. In the event of a merger, acquisition, or sale of our business, your data may also be transferred. In the event we become the subject of an insolvency proceeding, whether voluntary or involuntary, we or our liquidator, administrator, receiver or administrative receiver may sell, license or otherwise dispose of, such information in a transaction approved by the court. 

Your data may be transferred to and maintained on computers located outside of your state, country, or other governmental jurisdiction where the data protection laws may differ from those of your jurisdiction. If you are located outside United States, please note that the data we collect through the Site may be processed in and outside of the United States. We will take all the steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy and that no transfer of your data will take place to an organization or a country unless there are adequate controls in place including the security of your data. Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer. 

**Security** 

We take strong precautions and measures to protect the security of your personal information and to ensure that your choices for its intended use are honored, and to protect your data from loss, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure, alteration, or destruction. The security of your data is important to us but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your data, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. As a result, you acknowledge that there are security and privacy limitations of the Internet which are beyond our control; the security, integrity and privacy of any and all information and data exchanged between you and us through this Site cannot be guaranteed; and any such information and data may be viewed or tampered with in transit by a third party. We make no warranty, express, implied, or otherwise, regarding the security of the Site and your personal information.  

**Children** 

You must be an adult of 18 years or older to use the Site. We do not target the Site (or any of the Gold Alliance Sites) to children. Consistent with the federal Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (“COPPA”), we will never knowingly collect personal information from anyone under the age of 13 without requesting parental consent.  If you are aware that your minor child under the age of 13 has provided us with personal information, please contact us.

**California Residents – Your Privacy Rights**
----------------------------------------------

This portion is specific and applies only to web visitors of the Site who are California residents, under the meaning of Section 17014 of Title 18 of the Cal. Code of Regulations. We may revise this section from time to time as implementing regulations further develop and come into effect and we are able to provide you with better information on your CCPA rights and how to exercise them. 

If you are a California resident under the meaning of Section 17014 of Title 18 of the Cal. Code of Regulations, your use of the Site is subject to the California Consumer Privacy Act (“CCPA”), and all final, implementing regulations.  

Under the CCPA, a consumer has the following rights: 

(A) Notice at Collection: at or before the point of collection, the right to receive notice of our practices, including the categories of personal information and any sensitive personal information to be collected; the purposes for which such information is collected or used; whether such information is sold or shared; and the length of time that such information is retained. This information is found within this section. 

(B) Right to Know What Personal Information is Collected & Right to Access Personal Information: The right to know what personal information the business has collected about the consumer, including the categories of personal information, categories of sources from which the personal information is collected, the business or commercial purpose for collecting, selling, or sharing personal information, the categories of third parties to whom the business discloses personal information, and the specific pieces of personal information the business has collected about the consumer; 

(C) Right to Delete: The right to request that a business delete personal information that the business has collected from the consumer, subject to certain exceptions; 

(D) Right to Correct: The right to correct inaccurate personal information that a business maintains about a consumer; 

(E) Right to Opt-Out of the Sale or Sharing of Personal Information: if the business sells or shares personal information, the right to opt-out of the sale or sharing of personal information by the business;  

(F) Right to Limit the Use or Disclosure of Sensitive Personal Information: if the business uses or discloses sensitive personal information for reasons other than those in § 7027(m), the right to limit the use or disclosure of such sensitive personal information; and  

(G) Right to No Discrimination: The right not to receive discriminatory treatment by the business for the exercise of CCPA privacy rights.  

Information regarding our collection, disclosure, and sale/sharing practices are detailed below, in addition to instructions on how to exercise your CCPA rights. 

**What Personal Information Do We Collect?**

We have collected personal information about our visitors within the preceding twelve (12) months in the above categories detailed in the chart under the **“Personal Information We Collect About You and How We Use It”** heading above. 

**What Personal Information Do We Disclose?**

We have disclosed the following categories of personal information for a business purpose to the following categories of third parties in the preceding twelve (12) months.: We do/do not use or disclose sensitive personal information for purposes other than those specific in Section 7027(m).  

| Categories of Personal Information (PI) | Categories of Third Parties to Whom Such PI is Disclosed | Specific Business or Commercial Purpose for Disclosure |
| --- | --- | --- |
| Identifiers (e.g., a real name, alias, postal address, unique personal identifier, online identifier, Internet Protocol address, email address, account name, social security number, driver’s license number, passport number, or other similar identifiers), or information that identifies, relates to, describes, or is capable of being associated with, a particular individual | Email marketers/email marketing partners  <br>  <br>email service providers  <br>  <br>advertising networks  <br>  <br>payment processors  <br>  <br>data analytics providers | ​Auditing related to counting ad impressions to unique visitors, verifying positioning and quality of ad impressions, and auditing compliance with this specification and other standards  <br>  <br>Performing services on behalf of the business or service provider, including maintaining or servicing accounts, providing customer service, processing or fulfilling orders and transactions, verifying customer information, processing payments, providing financing, providing advertising or marketing services, providing analytic services, or providing similar services on behalf of the business or service provider. |
| Characteristics of protected classifications under California or federal law | Not applicable (not disclosed) |     |
| Commercial information (e.g., records of personal property, products or services purchased, obtained, or considered, or other purchasing or consuming histories or tendencies) | email marketers/email marketing partners;  <br>  <br>​​email service providers;  <br>  <br>advertising networks;  <br>  <br>data analytics providers | Auditing related to counting ad impressions to unique visitors, verifying positioning and quality of ad impressions, and auditing compliance with this specification and other standards  <br>  <br>Performing services on behalf of the business or service provider, including maintaining or servicing accounts, providing customer service, processing or fulfilling orders and transactions, verifying customer information, processing payments, providing financing, providing advertising or marketing services, providing analytic services, or providing similar services on behalf of the business or service provider. |
| Biometric information | Not applicable (not disclosed) |     |
| Internet or other electronic network activity information (e.g., browsing history, search history, and information regarding a consumer’s interaction with an Internet Web site, application, or advertisement) | Email marketers/email marketing partners  <br>  <br>email service providers  <br>  <br>advertising networks  <br>  <br>data analytics providers | Auditing related to counting ad impressions to unique visitors, verifying positioning and quality of ad impressions, and auditing compliance with this specification and other standards  <br>  <br>Performing services on behalf of the business or service provider, including maintaining or servicing accounts, providing customer service, processing or fulfilling orders and transactions, verifying customer information, processing payments, providing financing, providing advertising or marketing services, providing analytic services, or providing similar services on behalf of the business or service provider. |
| Geolocation data | email marketers/email marketing partners  <br>  <br>email service providers  <br>  <br>advertising networks  <br>  <br>data analytics providers | Auditing related to counting ad impressions to unique visitors, verifying positioning and quality of ad impressions, and auditing compliance with this specification and other standards  <br>  <br>Performing services on behalf of the business or service provider, including maintaining or servicing accounts, providing customer service, processing or fulfilling orders and transactions, verifying customer information, processing payments, providing financing, providing advertising or marketing services, providing analytic services, or providing similar services on behalf of the business or service provider. |
| Audio, electronic, visual, thermal, olfactory, or similar information | Not applicable (not disclosed) |     |
| Professional or employment-related information | Not applicable (not disclosed) |     |
| Education information | Not applicable (not disclosed) |     |
| Inferences drawn from any of the above information to create a profile about a consumer reflecting the consumer's preferences, characteristics, behavior, etc. | email marketers/email marketing partners  <br>  <br>email service providers  <br>  <br>advertising networks  <br>  <br>data analytics providers | Auditing related to counting ad impressions to unique visitors, verifying positioning and quality of ad impressions, and auditing compliance with this specification and other standards  <br>  <br>Performing services on behalf of the business or service provider, including maintaining or servicing accounts, providing customer service, processing or fulfilling orders and transactions, verifying customer information, processing payments, providing financing, providing advertising or marketing services, providing analytic services, or providing similar services on behalf of the business or service provider. |
| Sensitive personal information | Not applicable (not disclosed) |     |

**What Personal Information Do We Sell or Share?**

We have not sold or shared any personal information for a business purpose in the preceding 12 months. We do not have any actual knowledge of the sale or sharing of personal information of consumers under 16 years of age.  

**Notice of Right to Opt-out of Sale/Sharing**

You have the right to opt-out of the sale or sharing of your personal information. You have the right to direct a business that sells or shares your personal information to stop selling or sharing your personal information, and to refrain from doing so in the future. We process opt-out preference signals in a frictionless manner. All email communications from ActiveCampaign include a one click unsubscribe link. In addition, all SMS messages include the ability to opt out as well. Anyone contacted by Gold Alliance can request to be placed on a Do Not Call list that is maintained by Gold Alliance. They can make this request verbally, by email or by SMS.  You may also submit a request to opt-out of the sale/sharing by emailing us at [privacy@goldalliance.com](mailto:privacy@goldalliance.com).  

**How to Submit a Request Under the CCPA**

To submit a request to know, request to delete, and/or request to correct, you may email us at [privacy@goldalliance.com](mailto:privacy@goldalliance.com). To process your request, we may require that you submit the following information in conjunction with your request: your first name, last name, a California address, and email address. The information which you provide will be used to verify your request and to attempt to identify you within our data records. The information which you submit in conjunction with your request to know will be used for the express purposes of verification and providing you with responsive information to your request, if required. Please note that we utilize a two-step process for requests to delete, whereby you first submit your request to delete, and second, you separately confirm that you want your personal information deleted. The CCPA permits requests to know regarding collection and sale or sharing from the same consumer no more than twice in a twelve (12) month period.  

**How an Authorized Agent Can Make a Request Under the CCPA**

If you elect to use an authorized agent to exercise your right to submit a request to know, request to delete, and/or request to correct, before processing the request, we require the purported authorized agent to provide proof of your signed permission to submit the request (unless there is a power of attorney in place pursuant to Probate Code §§ 4121-4130). We also require that you directly verify your own identity with us, and directly confirm with us that you provided the authorized agent permission to submit the request on your behalf. The information submitted will not be used for any purposes other than to verify the request, fulfill the request, and fraud prevention. 

**Updates**

This Privacy Policy was published and last updated as of the date indicated at the top. We may update this Privacy Policy and its sections from time to time. Updates to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this Site and this Privacy Policy periodically and to be aware of any modifications. Your use of the Site after such modifications will constitute your acknowledgment of the modified Privacy Policy; and agreement to abide and be bound by the modified Privacy Policy. 

**Contact Us**

If you have any questions or concerns regarding your privacy rights or our Privacy Policy or practices, you may contact us via email at privacy@goldalliance.com, or by mail at 5550 Topanga Canyon Blvd., Suite 100, Woodland Hills, CA 91367.  

**Need More Information or Do You Need Extra Help?**

Further, if you have a disability which interferes with your ability to access this policy, we can make accommodations to present the policy in an alternative format to assist you. If you would like to receive this Privacy Policy in another format that is accessible to your needs (for example: audio, large print, etc.), please contact us. 

© 2023 www.goldalliance.com. All rights reserved.  

50 W. Liberty St. Suite 420  
Reno, NV 89501

Explore Gold IRAs
-----------------

DISCOVER
--------

Get in touch with us
--------------------

"\*" indicates required fields

First Name\*

Last Name\*

Phone\*

Email Address\*

Message\*

BWS reCaptcha

Send Your Message

By clicking the link above you agree by electronic signature to our [Terms & Conditions](https://goldalliance.com/terms-conditions) (including our arbitration provision and E-SIGN consent) and [Privacy Policy](https://goldalliance.com/privacy-policy) and give your express written consent (not required as a condition to purchase goods or services) for us to contact you (incl. via an automated telephone dialing system and text msgs) via telephone, mobile device, and/or email, even if your phone is on a Do Not Call registry, and to the recording of calls.  Alternatively, you may call us at 888-734-7453.

Please note that although Gold Alliance and its representatives are precious metals specialists, we are not licensed or registered investment advisers, attorneys, CPA's, or other financial service professionals. We do not give any tax, financial, legal or investment advice. Additionally, be aware that precious metals, like any investment, carry risk of loss and are not a suitable investment for everyone. Past performance is not necessarily indicative of future results and precious metals may appreciate, depreciate, or stay the same depending on a variety of factors. Anyone who considers purchasing Precious metals, Gold American Eagles, Proof Gold American Eagles, certified gold coins, as well as gold and silver bars should consider and carefully evaluate the associated risks and acquisition costs before making the investment, and you should always consult your financial and tax professional and carefully evaluate all risks associated with the acquisition of precious metals before making the investment. It is Gold Alliance’s view that precious metals should be considered a long-term investment, and that while you can sell your precious metals at any time, you should be prepared and willing to hold any purchased precious metals for several years before selling them. Gold Alliance cannot guarantee, and makes no representation, that any metals purchased (i.e. .999 gold bars, .9999 silver bars, or any gold or silver coins) will appreciate at all or appreciate sufficiently to produce a profit above and beyond the markup/ commissions charged whether they are bought for direct delivery or inside of a precious metals IRA. The decision to purchase or sell precious metals with funds outside or inside of a Gold IRA or a Gold Backed IRA, and which precious metals to purchase or sell, are the customer’s decision alone, and purchases and sales should be made subject to the customer's own research, prudence, and judgment. By accessing any Gold Alliance content, you agree to be bound by the terms of service. For questions regarding this disclaimer or this website please contact us at 888-567-6689.

© 2024 Gold Alliance. All rights reserved.
